Guide to the Edwin Warriner Papers and Photographs, 1790-1958 1977.255
Brooklyn Historical Society
- 1. Notes and Ephemera, 1791-1940; 5.42 Linear Feet
  - Lee, Wilson (23) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Lee, Peter (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Leek, John W. (24) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Le Fevre, John W. (25) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Leigh, Charles C. (26) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lent, Isaac H. (27) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lent, J. R. (27A) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Lent, Marvin R. (28) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Levings, Noah C. (29) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Nathaniel C. (30) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Liebhart, Henry (31) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lightbourn, Albert W. (32) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Little, J. Henry (33) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Little Neck African M. E. Church (34) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Little Neck African M. E. Zion Church (34A) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Little Neck Circuit M. E. Church (35) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Little Neck M. E. Church (36) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Littlewood, Thomas D. (37) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Livingston, Henry M. (37A) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lloyds Neck (38) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Long Island City, Second Church (47) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Long Island City, Third M. E. Church (48) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Long Island District (49) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Long Island North District (50) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Long Island South District (51) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Longking, Joseph (52) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Long Swamp (53) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Loomis, George W. (54) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Loomis, Reuben H. (55) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Losee, William (56) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Lounsbury, E. F. (57) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lovejoy, John (58) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Luckey, John (59) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Luckey, Samuel (image included) (60) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Lutz, John G. (61) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Lyon, John Christian (62) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Lyon, Jonathan (63) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Lyon, Moses A. (64) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - MacGregor, Duncan (1) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Mac Millan, James (1A) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - MacReading, Charles S. (2) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Maffit, John (3) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Magronigle, W. H. (4) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Mains, George P. (5) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Mallary, E. Dewitt (6) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Mallory, Charles T. (7) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Manaton, Richard K. (8) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Manetto Hill (9) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Manhasset African M. E. Zion Church (10) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Manhasset M. E. Preaching Place (11) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Manor (12) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Manorville Meth. Prot. Church (13) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Misiquog, see Suffolk Circuit (13A) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Manship, Winfield S. (14) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Marshall, Joseph D. (15) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Martindale, Stephen (16) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Mason, Thomas (16A) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Maspeth African M. E. Church (17) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Maspeth M. E. Church (18) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Matthias, John Barnett (19) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Matthias, John Jarvis (20) (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - McClume, Alex (30) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Mead, Nathaniel Jr. (44) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Melville (Sweet Hallow) (45) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Meredith, Richard (46) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Meredith, Samuel (47) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Merrick, John (49) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Merwin, John B. (50) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Merwin, Samuel (51) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Nadal, Bernard Harrison (image included) (1) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Nash, Albert (2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Nash, John (2A) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Near Jerusalem, see Bellmore (2B) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Near Rockaway, see Rockville Center (2-1/2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Julius (3) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Bridge, see Bellmore (4) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New Bushwick M. E. Class (4A) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New Lots, see Brooklyn Wesley Mission (4B) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Newtown M. E. Church (4B) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Newtown Circuit M. E. Church (5) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New Suffolk (6) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New Utrecht, see Bay Ridge (8) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New Village, a part of Lakeville Society (9) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Nichols, Andrew (10) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nichols, H. F. (10A) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nichols, Jarvis Z. (11) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Nichols Patent, same as Islip East, see Islip (12) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Nickerson, Lorenzo D. (13) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nixon, John (14) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Norris, William Henry (15) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - North Amityville M. E. Church, see Amityville (16) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - North East (17) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - North Hempstead Circuit (18) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Northport Circuit (19) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Northrop, Beardsley (20) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Northport M. E. Church (21) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Norwich and Oyster Bay Circuit (22) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Norwich, see East Norwich (23) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Oakdale (1) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Oakley, Peter (2) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Oak Neck, see Bayville (2A) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Old Field, see Suffolk Circuit (2C) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Odell, Joseph (2B) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Oldrin, Edward (3) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Oliver, Anna (3-1/4) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Olmstead, Miles (3-1/2) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Orchard, Nicholas (4) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Orcutt, Samuel (4A) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Orient M. E. Church (5) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Osbon, Abiathan M. (6) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Osborn, David (7) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Osborn, Elbert (8) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Osborn, Theron (9) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Osborn, Thomas Gilbert (10) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ostrander, Daniel (10-1/4) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Overbaugh, Frank C. (11-1/2) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Oyster Bay African M. E. Zion Church (12) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Oyster Bay M. E. Church (13) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Oyster Bay South M. E. Church (14) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Oyster Pond, see Orient (14) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Palmer, A. J. (1) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Palmer, Joseph (2) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Pardington, Raymer S. (3) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Parker, John (4) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Parker, Lindsay (5) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Pastors, Chronological List (9) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Patchogue Circuit (image included) (10) (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Includes a 1940 souvenir program from the Patchogue Methodist Church.
  - Payne, Charles H. (image included) (12) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Pearce, Aaron (13) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Pearsalls, formerly Rockaway Circuit (image included) (14) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Pease, Lewis (15) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Pease, Hart F. (15) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Pease, John M. (16) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Peck, George (18) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Peck, John L. (19) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Peck, John O. (20) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Pegg, John Jr. (22) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Pelton, Charles F. (23) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Perrine, John E. (24) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Perry, James H. (image included) (25) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Perry, Levi P. (26) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Perry, Salmon C. (27) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Peterson, Ole P. (28) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Phoebus, William (29) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Phillips, E. E (30) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Phillips, Watson L. (31) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Pierce, E. B. (32) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Peirce, Gershom (33) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Peirce, Ralph (34) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Pierce, Robert (35) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Piermont African M. E. Zion Church (36) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Pilkington, John (37) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Pilmoor, Joseph (38) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Pilsbury, Benjamin (39) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Plain Edge, German Methodist Mission (40) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Plain Edge M. E. Church (41) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Plain Edge Meth. Prot. Church (42) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Plain View, formerly Manetto Hill (42A) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Port Jefferson Circuit (48) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Port Washington African M. E. Church (50) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Port Washington Congregational Meth. Church (51) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Port Washington M. E. Church (52) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Poulson, Thomas L. (53) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Povey, J. (54) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Powell, Benjamin W. (55) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Powell, Charles W. (56) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pratt, George N. (57) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Pray, William T. (58) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Reed, George Edward (image only) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds, John (21) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds, Reuben (22) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds, Rufus K. (23) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Remington, S. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Includes Remington's acknowledgement of receipt of table allowance (1837).
  - Rice, Nathan (24) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rice, Phineas (25) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Richardson, Henry (26) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Richardson, Lemuel (27) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Richardson, Marvin (28) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Richmond, Stephen (28A) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Rickhow, Jacob (28B) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Riehl, Karl (28C) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rippere, John (29) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - River Dam (30) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Riverhead African M. E. Zion Church (31) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Riverhead and Jamesport Circuit (32) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Riverhead Free Methodist Church (11) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Riverhead M. E. Church (33) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Roberts, George (35) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Roberts, Henry F. (36) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Roberts, Robert (37) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Robertson, Jay F. (37A) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, David (38) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, George C. (39) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, James (40) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Jonathan N. (41) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, William J. (42) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rockaway (or Rockville Center) Circuit (43) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Includes the Constitution and By-laws of the Female Aid Society of the M. E. Church of Rockaway, L.I. (1859). Includes the record of subscribers supporting the building of a new church (1866).
  - Rockville Center Circuit, see Rockaway Circuit (44) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rockville Center First Methodist Church (image included) (45) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rockville Center Meth Prot Church (46) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rye (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Sadlier, A. (1) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Sag Harbor African M. E. Church (2) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Sag Harbor African M. E. Zion Church (3) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Sag Harbor Circuit (4) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Sag Harbor M. E. Church (image included) (5) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Saint James (6) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Salisbury, Lodowick (7) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sandford, Peter P. (8) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Sand Hill Church (9) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Sand Hole Church (10) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Sandford, Isaac (14) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Saunders, James W. (15) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Savage, William L. (16) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Saxton, Otis (17) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sayville Circuit (18) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sayville M. E. Church (19) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Scholefield, Arnold (22) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Scofield, Frank A. (23) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Scofield, Henry (24) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Scofield, Seth W. (25) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Scofield, W. E. (26) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Scott, Jacob (27) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Scudder, Moses L. (28) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Sea Cliff M. E. Church (29) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Seaford (30) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Seaman, Richard (31) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Seaman, Samuel A. (32) (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Includes Seaman's transcriptions of baptismal records from the "Old Book" of John (Pt.?).
  - Searingtown M. E. Church (33) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Stoddard, Parley (34) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Stony Brook African M. E. Church (35) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Seney, Robert (36) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Stony Brook Meth Prot Church (39) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Shaffer, James N. (image included) (42) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Simons Neck (42) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Shaw, Jacob (43) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Sheepshead Bay M. E. Church (image included) (44) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Shelling, Charles (45) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Shelter Island (46) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Snediker, Seaman N. (1) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Snethen, Nicholas (2) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Sodorn, see Baldwins (3) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Somers, P. P. (4) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - South Hampton M. E. Church (5) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - South Haven Circuit (6) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Southold and Cutchogue Circuit (7) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Southold M. E. Church (image included) (9) (Box 12, Folder 3, 4)
  - Southport (10) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - South Rayner, see Freeport (11) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Spencer, John C. (12) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Speonk, see West Hampton (13) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Speonk Prot. Meth. (14) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Springfield M. E. Church (15) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Squiretown (16) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Stahl, Philip (17) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stansbury, John H. (18) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Staple, Mark (19) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Starr, Orlando (20) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Stearns, Charles (21) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Stebbius, Cyrus (22) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Steele, William C. (23) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Stephenson, Thomas (24) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Stevens, Abel (image included) (25) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Stevens, Alex C. (26) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Stevens, David (26A) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Stevens, David I. (27) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Stewart, Lalmon (28) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Stiehler, Frederick (29) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Still, Henry S. (30) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Stillman, George (31) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Stillman, Stephen L. (32) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Stillwellites (32A) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Stopford, William Kennedy (40) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Stout, Edward S. (41) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Stowe, Leroy S. (42) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Stowe, W. F. (43) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Stratton, John S. (44) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Strebeck, George (45) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Streeter, Lewis R. (46) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Studley, William S. (47) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Success, Flushing Circuit (48) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Suffolk County Preacher's Meeting (49A) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Summerfield, John (50) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Swahlen, John (51) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sweeney, James (52) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sweet Hollows, see Melville (53) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sykes, Oliver (54) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Smith, W. H. M. (72) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Smithtown Branch (73) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Smithtown Hauppauge, see Hauppauge (75) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Smithville, see Amityville and New Bridge Circuit (77) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Tackaberry, John C. (1) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Taft, W. N. (2) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, Bazeleele (2A) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, David (3) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Terry, David (3-1/2) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, George (4) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Terry, Thomas Morris (5) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Thacher, William (6) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Thomas, Joseph C. (7) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Thomas, Noble W. (8) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Thomas, Samuel (9) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Thomas, William H. (10) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, George L. (11) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, John R. (image included) (12) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, Robert R. (13) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Thompson, Samuel (14) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Tomkinson, William E. (16) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Tompkins, Nehemiah U. (19) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Tomlinson, Charles (20) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Toppingtown M. E. Church Colored Class (21) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Totten, Joseph (22) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Tower, Freeman P. (23) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Townsend, Frank S. (24) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Traumer, J. N. (25) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Travis, Robert (26) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trieder, Christian O. (27) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trimming Square, see Hempstead M. E. Church (28) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trippett, John (29) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - True, Charles K. (30) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Trumble, William (30A) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tunnell, John (31) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Turner, Chester W. (32) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Turnpike Class (33) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Turtle Hook, see Uniondale (34) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tuthill, David (35) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Twidley, William (36) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Uniondale, formerly Turtle Hook (37) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Union Place Mission (38) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Unionville, formerly Gravesend (39) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Upham, F. B. (39-1/2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Valley Stream (40) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Van Nostrand, Albert (42) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Veritytown, see Seaford (42A) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vincent, Leonard W. (43) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vincent, Marvin R. (44) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vosselles, D. B. (45) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Wake, Jr., Richard (1) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Wake, Richard (2) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Wake, William (3) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Walker, Gerry (4) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Wallon, Louis (5) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ward, Francis (6) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Ward, F. J. (7) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Wardell, William H. (8) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Warden, William M. (9) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ware, Francis W. (10) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ware, Thomas (11) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Warren, Henry W. (12) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Warriner, Edwin (13) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Washburn, Ebenezer (14) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square M. E. Class, Hempstead (15) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Watkins, William F. (16) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Watt, Ephraim (17) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Watt, Thomas John (18) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Webb, Thomas (19) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Webster, William R. (20) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Weck, Jacob (21) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Weeksville African M. E. Church, East Brooklyn (23) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Weeksville African M. E. Zion Church (24) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Weeksville Circuit (25) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Westbury M. E. Church (26) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Westfield M. E. Church, see Coram (27) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Westgate, George L. (28) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Weston. Samuel (28A) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Westville Meth Prot Church, see Inwood (29) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - West Hampton Circuit M. E. Church (30) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - West Hills M. E. Church (31) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Whatcoat, Richard (33) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Whedon, David D. (34) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Whedon, John S. (35) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Whelain, Daniel (36) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - White, Nicholas (37) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Whitecar, Charles H. (38) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Whitefield, George (39) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Whitehead, Stephen G. (40) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Whitehead, Thomas (41) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Whitestone M. E. Church (42) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Wild, Joseph (43) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Wildey, Joseph (44) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Wilford, Madison (44A) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Willdridge, H, A. (45) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Willett, William M. (46) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Williams, Christopher S. (47) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Williams, Robert (48) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Williamsburg African M. E. Church (49) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg African M. E. Zion Church (50) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg Circuit M. E. Church (51) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg City Mission (52) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg M. E Church (53) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg German M. E. Mission (54) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Willing, Matthias E. (55) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Willis, Henry (56) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Wilson, Benjamin (57) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Wilson, John (58) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Wilson, William Crawford (59) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Windsor Terrace (60) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Winfield M. E. Church (61) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Wing, Charles S. (62) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Withey, Ezra (63) (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Woerz, Godfrey J. (64) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Wolff, Jacob L. (65) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Wood, John W. B. (66) (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Woodbury (67) (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Woodhaven Meth Prot Church (68) (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Woodruff, George W. (69) (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Woodsburgh M. E. Church (70) (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Woodsburgh Meth Prot Church (71) (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Woolsey, Elijah (72) (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Woolves Hollow, see Brookhaven (73) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Worth, Justus O. (74) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Wright, Daniel I. (75) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Wright, E. S. (76) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Wright, Henry N. (77) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Wright, Richard (77A) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Wyatt, Albert H. (78) (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Wymond, Richard (79) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Yarrow, W. H. (80) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Yellow Hook, see Bay Ridge (81) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Unidentified Miscellaneous Documents (Box 13, Folder 50)
- 2. Photographs and Other Images, circa 1850-circa 1890; 0.41 Linear Feet
  This series contains around 200 images of various ministers and churches. The visual materials consist of photographs, tintypes, cabinet cards, cartes des visites, engravings, clippings from printed material, and drawings. The bulk of the images are undated.
  The series is arranged in alphabetical order by subject. Because the bulk, perhaps all, of the images are undated, but date from sometime in the second half of the nineteenth century, the container list does not include a date range.
  - Abbot, A.V.R. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Ira (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Arnold, Smith (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bangs, Herman (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bangs, William H. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bangs, William McKendree (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Barnes, Samuel C. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Barton, William (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bass, Job G. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bates, Edmund Ogden (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Beach, Anson Frost (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bethel, T. W. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Booth, John F. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bouton, James David (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Breckenridge, J. C. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brower, Calvin R. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Charles S. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Frederick (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Jacob (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 1)
  - Brown, O. E. (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 1)
  - Buck, C. H. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buckelen, J. R. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buckley, James M. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Buffett, Phoebe (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Burton, H. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Carpenter, James and Wife (Box Cartes de Visite 1, Folder 2)
  - Chase, Henry (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cheney, Laban C. (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 2)
  - Clark, F. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Theodosius (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Clark, W. W. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Coburn, George L. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Codling, R. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Coles, G. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Collard, G. W. (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Collard, James (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 3)
  - Collins, Judson Dwight (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Collins, W. F. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Corbit, William (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Covel, Jr., J. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Crawford, John (Box Cabinet Cards 1, Folder 1)
  - Creagh, B (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Crooks, G. R. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Curry (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - D'Orsay, J. S. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - De La Matyr (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Devinne, D (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Diossey (Box Tintypes 1, Folder 4)
  - Eagan, A. R. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fennell, James (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ferris, D. O. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Filmer, G (Box 14, Folder 3)